{
    "name": "Tabellone Leopardy",
    "categories": ["Geografia", "Sport", "Videogiochi", "Film"],
    "rows": [
      {
        "points": "Punti 100",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "UXVhbCDDpGxhIGNhcGl0YWxlIGQnSXRhbGlhPw==",
            "answer": "Um9tYQ=="
          },
          {
            "question": "UXVhbnRpIGdpb2NhdG9yZSBjaSBzYSBjaW8gaW4gdW5hIHNxdWFkcmEgZCBjYWxjby8=",
            "answer": "MTE="
          },
          {
            "question": "UXVhbCDDpGxlIGF6aWVuZGEgaGEgc3ZlbGxvcHBhdG8gJ1N1cGVyIE1hcmlvIEJyb3MnPw==",
            "answer": "TmludGVuZG8="
          },
          {
            "question": "Q2hpIGhhIGludGVycHJldGF0byBpbCBydWxpbyBkZSBBamNrIERhdXNvbiBpbiAnVGl0YW5pYy8=",
            "answer": "TGVvbmFyZG8gRGlDYXByaW8="
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "points": "Punti 200",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "UXVhbCDDpGxhIGZpZHVtZSBIw6RwbHVzbHVuZ3RvZCdFdXJvcGE/",
            "answer": "Vm9sZ2E="
          },
          {
            "question": "SW4gY2hlIHNwb3J0IHNpIHVzYSB1bmEgcmFjY2hldHRhPw==",
            "answer": "VGVubmlz"
          },
          {
            "question": "UXVhbCDDpGxlIGlsIHZpZGVvZ2lhY28gZGkgcm9sb8OpIHBsdSBmYXN1b3M/",
            "answer": "RmluYWwgRmFudGFzeQ=="
          },
          {
            "question": "UXVhbCDDpGxlIGlsIGZpbG0gw6JpIGZpc3RvIGFsIGNpbmVtYT8=",
            "answer": "QXZhdGFy"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "points": "Punti 300",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "UXVhbCDDpGxhIGxhIG1vbnRhbmdhIMOpIGFsdGEgZGVsIG1vbmRvPw==",
            "answer": "RXZlcmVzdA=="
          },
          {
            "question": "SW4gcXVhbGUgc3BvcnQgc2kgaWZmZWN0dWFtZW50byB1biAnc2xhbSBkdW5rJz8=",
            "answer": "QmFza2V0YmFsbA=="
          },
          {
            "question": "UXVhbCDDpGxlIGNvbnNvbGUgaGEgcml2b2x1emlhdMOtIGlsIG1vbmRvIGRpIHZpZGVvZ2lhY28gZGVsbCBhbm5pICc5MCc/",
            "answer": "UGxheVN0YXRpb24="
          },
          {
            "question": "Q2hpIGhhIGRpcmV0dG8gaWwgcGFkcmlubyA/",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNpcyBGb3JkIENvcHBvbGE="
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "points": "Punti 400",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "UXVhbCDDpGxhIGlsIGRlcyBhbWVudG8gcMOibiBncmFudGUgZGVsIG1vbmRvPw==",
            "answer": "U2FoYXJh"
          },
          {
            "question": "SW4gY2hlIHNwb3J0IHNpIHVzYSBsZSBtYXp6ZSBkYSBiYXNlYmFsbD8=",
            "answer": "QmFzZWJhbGw="
          },
          {
            "question": "UXVhbCDDpGxlIHZpZGVvZ2lhY28gaGEgY29tZSBwcm9kdXN0YSAnTWFzdGVyIENoZWlmJz8=",
            "answer": "SGFsbw=="
          },
          {
            "question": "UXVhbCDDpGxlIGlsIGZpbG0gZCdhbmltYXRpb25lIMOpIHByYW1pYWRvIGRlbGxhIERpc25leT8=",
            "answer": "SWwgUmUgTGVvbmU="
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
  